1. request = findTestObject("Object Repository/API AI Demo/Users/GET - Get all users")
5. logInfo(Sending GET request to: $request.getRestUrl())
9. response = sendRequest(request)
13. statusCode = response.getStatusCode()
17. logInfo(Response status code: $statusCode)
21. if (statusCode != 200)
25. responseBody = response.getResponseBodyContent()
29. logInfo(Response body (raw): $responseBody)
33. parsed = JsonSlurper().parseText(responseBody)
37. usernames = []
41. if (parsed instanceof java.util.List)
1. parsed.each()
45. logInfo(Extracted usernames ($usernames.size()): $usernames)
49. expectedUsername = "bankinguser123"
53. exists = usernames.contains(expectedUsername)
57. logInfo(Username '$expectedUsername' present: $exists)
61. if (!(exists))
1. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseId())
5. println(testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus())